{
  "MultipleChoice": [
    {
      "question": "In a window, at the top is the _____, immediately below it is the _____.",
      "choice1": "Toolbar, Titlebar",
      "choice2": "Titlebar, Toolbar",
      "choice3": "Titlebar, Menubar",
      "choice4": "Menubar, Titlebar",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The _____ are a collection of shortcut icons for commonly used functions.",
      "choice1": "Text boxes",
      "choice2": "Toolbars",
      "choice3": "Tables",
      "choice4": "Cliparts",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The _____ are a collection of shortcut icons for commonly used functions.",
      "choice1": "Text boxes",
      "choice2": "Toolbars",
      "choice3": "Tables",
      "choice4": "Cliparts",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ is not a web page editor.",
      "choice1": "Adobe Pagemaker",
      "choice2": "MS Frontpage",
      "choice3": "Netscape Navigator",
      "choice4": "Netscape composer",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which instructs a Web browser on how to format and process a hypertext document?",
      "choice1": "Documents",
      "choice2": "Tags",
      "choice3": "Elements",
      "choice4": "Programs",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Web page editors are _____ application packages.",
      "choice1": "Data processing",
      "choice2": "System",
      "choice3": "Software",
      "choice4": "Hardware",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "With the help of a word processor we can save our work as",
      "choice1": "ASCII text file",
      "choice2": "Internet",
      "choice3": "Picture",
      "choice4": "Image",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the element content to be manipulated by the tags.",
      "choice1": "Text between the start tag and end tag",
      "choice2": "Text before the start tag",
      "choice3": "Text after the end tag",
      "choice4": "None of these",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many font sizes are permitted by HTML to display text?",
      "choice1": "3",
      "choice2": "5",
      "choice3": "6",
      "choice4": "7",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following specifies the space between the border of the cell and its contents?",
      "choice1": "CELLPADDING",
      "choice2": "CELLSPACING",
      "choice3": "BORDER",
      "choice4": "WIDTH",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ are like the drop down lists used in windows dialog boxes.",
      "choice1": "Menu controls",
      "choice2": "Radio button",
      "choice3": "Buttons",
      "choice4": "Password",
      "answer": 1
    }
  ],

  "TrueOrFalse": [
    {
      "question": "JavaScript is a programming language.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML 5 was first drafted in 2022.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML 5 was first drafted in 2022.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML 5 was first edited by Ian Hickson.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML 5 provides drag-and-drop effect.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " HTML mobile Ready.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML 5 has a total of 12 formatting tags.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Every HTML5 web page starts with the <doctype> declaration.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Comments in HTML begins with “<-” and ends with “->”.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Older HTML files work on newer browsers",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A hyperlink apply to text only.",
      "choice1": "TRUE",
      "choice2": "FALSE",
      "answer": 2
    }
  ],

  "Identificatio": [
    {
      "question": "Marquees tag works only with?",
      "answer": "Internet explorer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What level does the <H1> tag used to display heading?",
      "answer": "First Level"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tag is used to add an image to a document?",
      "answer": "<img>"
    },
    {
      "question": "<select> and </select> tags are used to create?",
      "answer": " List boxes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What list is enclosed with the <dl> and </dl> tags?",
      "answer": "Definition List"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tag is used to create row and column heading in a table?",
      "answer": "<th>"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the color combination of Tint?",
      "answer": "hue + white"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tag does the body of a HTML document end?",
      "answer": "</body>"
    },
    {
      "question": "What Attribute of the <meta> tag identifies the URL of the web page?",
      "answer": "url"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the end tag of a paragraph?",
      "answer": "</p>"
    }
  ]
}
